{"data":[{"question":"The old man is expecting with pleasure the visit of his grandchildrens.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"old","b":"expecting","c":"pleasure","d":"grandchildrens","answer":"4","explain":"- Grandchildrens-> grandchildren","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"My friend was crazy although he was informed of the news of his mother's death.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"crazy","b":"although","c":"informed","d":"death","answer":"2","explain":"- Althouth-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The soldier leaped into the water so soon as the ship touched the shore.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"leaped","b":"into","c":"so soon as","d":"touched","answer":"3","explain":"- As soon as-> before","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"His fondness for the game increase with his proficiency.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"fondness","b":"for","c":"increase","d":"proficiency","answer":"3","explain":"-Increase-> increases","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Her handwriting is so badly that I can't read.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"handwriting","b":"so","c":"badly","d":"can't","answer":"3","explain":"- So badly-> bad","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Although he is industrious, he hasn't successed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Although","b":"is","c":"industrious","d":"successed","answer":"4","explain":"- Successed-> succeeded","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Winning that prize have made him very conceited.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Winning","b":"have","c":"him","d":"conceited","answer":"2","explain":"- Have-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When he was a child, he loves dismantling things to see how they worked.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"loves","c":"to see","d":"how","answer":"2","explain":"- Loves-> loved","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"English people in general don't like complaining on public.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"people","b":"in","c":"don't","d":"on","answer":"4","explain":"- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We are moving to Bristol next week but we are promising to stay in contact with you.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are moving","b":"but","c":"are promising","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"- Are promising-> promise","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}